Subindex build by Linnet
-=伊甸园美剧论坛 http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-= http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -= http://ytet.org=- Proudly Presents
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: 饼饼 小朦 舞娘 校对: 葱家的小毛毛 时间轴: 哈露露露露
-= http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -= http://ytet.org=- Sync:哈露露露露
老爸老妈浪漫史 第七季第四集
How I Met Your Mother Season 7 Episode 04
-=伊甸园美剧论坛 http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-= http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -= http://ytet.org=- Proudly Presents
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: 饼饼 小朦 舞娘 校对: 葱家的小毛毛 时间轴: 哈露露露露
-= http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -= http://ytet.org=- Sync:哈露露露露
老爸老妈浪漫史 第七季第四集
How I Met Your Mother Season 7 Episode 04
我真不敢相信我居然来看心理医生
I can't believe I'm talking to a therapist.
我平常也不是一个很感性的人
Well,usually,I'm not the touchy-feely,talk-about-your-emotions type
但这次 我必须鼓起勇气承认 我的确需要帮助
but with this,I just had to be a big enough person to admit that I need help.
哦
Huh.
我想这就是成长的感觉吧
I guess this is what growing up feels like.
这是法院强令的心理咨询
This is court-mandated therapy.
你袭击了一位女性
You assaulted a woman.
哦...
Oh...
那件糗事
That silly thing.
我想我们可以谈谈那个
I guess we can talk about that.
是从几个月前开始的
It all began a few months ago.
这个人是Barney
There's this guy,Barney.
也是我的前男友
We used to date.
我向他介绍了我的同事 Nora
I set him up with this girl I work with,Nora.
Barney煞费苦心的向Nora证明 他会是一个好男朋友
Barney was working hard to prove he was real boyfriend material.
所以整周我都坐在那里
So,all week,I had to sit there watching him...
看他送花
send flowers...
送巧克力
chocolates...
送气球
balloons.
然后有一天...
Then one day...
嘿
Hey...
我听说Barney今天啥也没送
I heard Barney didn't send anything today.
Patrice说他可能劈腿了
Patrice said maybe he met somebody else.
她可真八卦 你说是不?
She's such a bitch,right?
* 当一个男人爱上一个女人 *
* When a man loves a woman *
* 他绝对不会一心两用 *
* Can't keep his mind on nothin' else *
他可真迷人
He's so dreamy.
没人问你 Patrice!
Nobody asked you,Patrice!
真不好意思 你肯定已经认为 我不是一个好人了
I'm sorry. You must already think that I'm a horrible person.
Robin 很多来我这儿看病的人 都是犯下重罪的
Robin,many of my patients are disturbed felons.
上周 有个人还给我寄了一包排泄物
Last week,one of them mailed me a bag of his feces.
但好的一面是 他记得我的生日
On the plus side,he remembered my birthday.
跟他们比 你做的还不算什么
You're doing fine.
最后 我忍无可忍
Well,finally,I-I just couldn't take it anymore.
彻底崩溃了
I snapped.
* 当一个男人 当这个男人 *
* When a man,when a man,when this man *
* 爱上一个女人 *
* Loves a woman! *
所以就在那时 你袭击她了?
And that's when the assault occurred?
不是
Not exactly.
这么说来你喝的酩酊大醉 躲在桌子底下 大吃偷来的巧克力
So,you're drunk under a desk,binge-eating stolen chocolates.
我讲的不是很明白 是吧?
Boy,I am not coming across great here,am I?
重点不是你讲明白没
This is not about how you're coming across.
不过也确实没讲明白
But no.
好吧 为了让你更明白  我必须讲下我的朋友Marshall和Lily
Okay,well,for this story to make sense,I have to tell you about my friends Marshall and Lily.
这酒看起来不错
The wine looks good.
嘿 嘿 孕妇不能喝酒
Hey,hey,hey,hey,pregnant women can't drink alcohol.
不是的 医生说偶尔尝一口也没差的
No,my doctor says it's okay to have a sip of wine every now and then.
真的吗?
Really?
Sonya医生太好了
Dr.Sonya's great.
每次问她可不可以吃东西 她就像这样...
Whenever you ask her if you can have something,she's,like...
可以吃点儿
Just a little bit.
等下  Sonya医生没允许你吃寿司 是吧?
Wait,Dr. Sonya doesn't let you have sushi,does she?
可以吃点儿
Just a little bit.
连奇多都还能吃?
You're allowed to have Cheetos?
奇多...
Cheetos...
啊 也可以吃点儿
Ah,just a little bit.
你不介意的话 为了以防万一 我可以再检查一下这个吗?
You mind if I double-check some of this stuff just in case?
作为我们宝宝计划的团队成员之一 我应该这么做
I mean,it's the least I could do as part of Team Baby.
" 宝宝计划 " ? 哇
"Team Baby"? Whoa.
下一步是什么  还有专门定制的团队T恤?
What's next,like,cheesy matching T-shirts?
没有啦
No.
Robin 那些连环杀手们 讲犯罪过程都比你快
Robin,I've had serial killers lead me to shallow graves faster than you're telling this story.
好啦!
Okay!
我是不能再跟Nora一起工作了
Look,it was getting impossible for me to be around Nora
所以 除掉Nora的机会来了...
so when an opportunity to get rid of her presented itself...
桑迪时间到!
It's Sandy time!
快围过来
Huddle up,gang.
两件事 第一  有人从我办公室偷了一瓶名贵的酒...
Two things: 1) Somebody stole a very expensive bottle of wine from my office...
第二 我需要有人去法国报导 八国集团峰会
2) I need a producer to cover the G8 Summit in France.
Nora可以的!
Nora will do it!
我知道虽然我是前辈 但是...
I mean,I know I have seniority,but...
我还是想问问Nora自己的意思
I was gonna ask Nora anyway.
Robin 谢谢你的支持
Thanks for the support,Robin.
这对我来说太重要了
This is huge for me.
Sandy 你确定?
Are,are you sure about this,Sandy?
我的确是个前辈
I do have seniority.
这我可以肯定
Oh,I'm sure.
Nora很迷人
Nora's amazing.
我想跟她上床
I want to have sex with her.
要先解决内心对Barney的醋意 而你老板都对她...
To deal with that rejection from Barney,not to mention your boss...
一定非常难受吧
must've really hurt.
我们为什么不研究一下这段情绪呢?
Why don't we dig into those emotions?
然后Marshall跟Lily去了 Sonya医生那儿...
So Marshall and Lily were at Dr. Sonya's office...
我对阴道的了解真是少的可怜
It's fascinating how profoundly little I know about vaginas.
请进
Come in.
Ted 你来这儿干什么?
Ted,what are you doing here?
我核对了这纸上的事情 这位" 医生" 说都没问题 但她却错了
I checked up on all the stuff this "doctor" says is okay,and she's wrong.
所以 为了孩子的健康 我来了
So,for the health of this baby,I'm stepping in.
- 听上去这个Ted该来看看心理医生了 - 哦 他的确得来
- Sounds like this Ted guy could benefit from some therapy. - Oh,he definitely could.
这简直不能接受
This is unacceptable.
对不起 我们得换个医生了
I'm sorry,we're gonna have to find a new doctor.
- 同志们 为了我们孩子的身体健康 - " 我们的" ?
Guys,for the health of our baby,Our?
我们得认真对待Lily吃进肚子里的东西
we have to get serious about what Lily is putting in her body.
说到这儿 当咱们生的时候 绝不能用麻药
Speaking of which,when we deliver,we won't be using any drugs.
闪一边儿去!
Get out!
干嘛这样对我?
Why are you kicking me out?
因为你总是破坏我们的甜蜜时刻
Because you're always intruding on our intimate moments!
这就又像是回到大学一样!
This is like college all over again!
我去 你们也太能整了!
Man,you guys sure are messy!
到处都是衣服
There's clothes everywhere.
门把手上居然还有袜子!
There's even a sock on the door!
门把手挂袜子是公认的 " 我们需要独处空间" 的暗号好吗?
A sock on the door is a universal code for "We need some space."
我们不仅那时候需要 现在也需要!
We needed it back then,and we need it now.
得了吧!
Come on!
我们是三剑客啊!
We're a trio!
我们一直都是三剑客啊!
We've always been a trio!
我们就好像蝙蝠侠  罗宾还有那个老管家
We're right up there with Batman and Robin and Alfred.
滚!
Out!
罗密欧 朱丽叶还有那个药剂师
Romeo and Juliet and the Apothecary.
滚!
Now!
我们就像盐 胡椒还有孜然
Salt and Pepper and Cumin!
那边的小东西是来干嘛的?
What's that little guy up there do?
哦 可怜的孩子
Oh,you poor girl.
Robin!
这些事都是一环扣一环的 我发誓
It all ties together,I swear.
然后 Nora就要去法国了
So,Nora was about to leave for France.
你知道吗 就在不久前 我还担心
You know,not too long ago,I would have been worried that
如果我把你留下的话 你的魂会被那些金发大波妹给勾走
if I left you alone,you'd be up to no good with some blond bimbo.
哦 我已经改过自新了
Oh,I've changed.
我知道 所以当我回来的时候
I know,which is why when I get back,it's gonna be the start of a new chapter for us.
咱俩的感情可以开启一个新篇章 只有我跟你 希望没有那条领带
A chapter of me and you and hopefully not that tie.
你说的对!
You got me!
一路顺风!
Have a nice trip!
Stinson医生吗?
Dr. Stinson?
我看了你的广告 我是来找你做免费缩胸咨询的
I saw your ad,and I'm here for my free breast-reduction consultation.
你觉着呢?
What do you think?
是不是太大了?
Are they too big?
我简直不敢相信 你还在勾搭那些胸大无脑的美女们!
I can't believe you're still running plays on dumb blondes!
我还以为你对Nora是认真的呢!
I thought you were serious about Nora!
我发誓我是认真的!
No,I've been good,I swear!
我只是忘了我的BDS
I just forgot about my BDSes.
BDS?
BDSes?
放荡女交付系统
Bimbo Delivery Systems.
你看 这么多年来 我一直致力于 开发一个精密的系统
You see,over the years,I've launched a variety of elaborate systems
能让我把到妹上床的
that are always working to get me laid.
比如说自动弹出的广告
Like my pop-up ads.
大家好
Oh,hi.
我是Barney Stinson医生
I'm Dr. Barney Stinson.
你的胸部有没有大到 让日常生活都困难重重呢
Are your really large breasts making everyday tasks difficult?
噢!
Oh!
现在有一个更好的解决办法!
There's just got to be a better way!
没错!
There is!
我 Barney Stinson医生 只要一点点时间
I,Dr. Barney Stinson,for a limited time only
就可以为您实行一个免费缩胸手术
can give you a free breast-reduction consultation.
打电话给我
Call me.
要是你的"门环"太大 交给我 我来搞定 它们
If your knockers are just too damn big,I can handle them...
它
it.
女人真的会这么相信这个吗?
Women actually fell for that?
没错
Yeah.
这项业务真的很成功
That business really took off.
在各种场合你都能见到
It played in all kinds of markets.
好啦 幸存者们 今天的奖励赛的奖品就是
Okay,survivors,today's reward challenge is brought to you by
免费获得Barney Stinson医生的缩胸治疗
Dr. Barney Stinson's Free Breast Reduction Consultations.
这个骗人的方法太成功了 它还催生了大量其他的方法
That scam was so successful,it spawned a related enterprise.
要是你被一个弟弟很大还自称
If you've been fooled by a well-endowed man
能做缩胸手术的医生骗了
who claimed to be a doctor offering free breast-reduction consultations
来找我吧 我是Arnie Linson律师 加入集体诉讼
come see me,Arnie Linson,attorney-at-law,and join my class-action suit.
如果你的大胸被虐待了 我能搞定 它们
If your giant breasts have been wronged,I can handle them...
它
it.
我让她们来了又来 哈哈
I got 'em comin' and goin'! Uh-huh.
我真不敢想像你 为了泡个妹子 要花这么多功夫
I can't believe you go to so much trouble to get laid.
是啊 有时候我连澡都懒得洗、
Yeah,sometimes I don't even have to shower.
妈妈就喜欢那股麝香味道
Mama loves it musky.
在Nora回来之前 我得把这些系统都抛掉
I gotta shut down all these systems before Nora gets back.
我该怎么在3天之内做到呢?
How am I gonna do all that in three days?
我帮你
I'll help you.
我觉得你可以在那个小表格上写 "病人无私帮助需要帮助的朋友"
Maybe you should write on your little chart there: "Patient selflessly tried to help a friend in need."
首先 这是一个填字游戏
First of all,this is a crossword puzzle.
其次 你其实是打算在那三天 把Barney抢回来吧
Secondly,you were clearly planning on using those three days to steal Barney back.
他是我朋友啊!
I am his friend!
你怎么能这么说呢!
How dare you!
去了哈佛你就觉得自己很聪明了是吧
God,you think you're so smart just because you went to Harvard
然后还去了普林斯顿大学 然后…
and then Princeton and then...
哇 又是哈佛
wow,Harvard again.
额 好吧
Okay,yes,fine.
我…我确实是想把他抢回来
I was... I was trying to steal him back.
这是好现象
This is good.
你终于开始说你自己的事情了 而不是Marshall和Lily在干嘛干嘛
You're finally opening up and talking about yourself,not just what Marshall and Lily were up to.
噢没错 那个时候  Marshall和Lily在叠衣服
Oh,yeah,so Marshall and Lily were folding laundry...
我错了…
That one's my fault.
那个什么…
You know...
没事
Never mind.
那个…
It's just...
算了
Forget it.
Marshall 你是个爽快人
Marshall,you're a grown-ass man.
你要说什么你就直说好啦
If you want to say something,just say it.
我真心疼Ted
I feel bad for Ted!
要是我妈妈在这她一定会问我怎么了
And if my mom were here,she would ask me what was wrong.
你心疼Ted?
You feel bad for Ted?
他感觉自己就是个多余的人
It's tough feeling like the third wheel.
好吧 首先 我确信Ted没事的
Okay,first of all,I'm sure Ted's fine.
哪个加盐和胡椒的时候 不带上孜然啊
Who eats salt and pepper without cumin?
其次 Ted老是跟Sonya医生做对
Second,Ted is way off base coming after Dr.Sonya.
我们都喜欢她!对吧?
We love her! Right?
别跟我说你也开始怀疑Sonya医生了
Don't tell me you're doubting Dr. Sonya!
有那么一点点
Just a little bit.
那是啥?
What's that thing?
对有些女人来说 这只是我父母的骨灰
Well,for some women,it was the ashes of my parents.
还有些人觉得这是 从温布尔顿得来的战利品
For others,it was the trophy from Wimbledon.
但是对一个胸大无脑的人来说 这两项都是
And believe it or not,for one busty dullard,it was both.
玩乐 巨大的器官 对位
Game,enormous set,match.
喂?
Hello?
对 没错 谢谢你打回来
Oh,yeah,thanks for calling me back.
Barney 是港务局的Mitch
Uh,Barney,It's Mitch from the Port Authority.
港务局亲爱的Mitch
Port Authority Mitch.
每当有一个大眼睛的农村女孩 怀着对百老汇的梦想走下公共汽车
You'd always call me whenever a wide-eyed farm girl would get off the bus with big dreams of Broadway
对星探可能会让她做的是握还是舔 感到茫然无措的时候 你就会打给我
and no idea what a "casting director" could legally ask her to do,hold or lick during an audition.
不好意思啊 老朋友 你的服务已经没有人需要了
I'm sorry,old friend,your services are no longer needed.
哦天!我要通过电话做这个
Oh,God,I can't believe I'm doing this over the phone!
我爱Marge和那些孩子
My love to Marge and the kids!
我懂的 来
I know. Here.
没想到这么难受
I didn't realize this would be so hard!
我明白 我了解
I know,I know.
但是 你也知道我们要实行清单上写的
But hey,you know what We're almost through our checklist.
- 好吗? - 嗯
- Okay? - Okay.
没事了
Okay?
对了 我想起来了 我当时干嘛 要打电话给发廊说"Jack Fantastic辞职了?"
Which reminds me,why am I calling a hair salon and saying,"Jack Fantastic is quitting"?
亲爱的 借用Maya Angelou一直 跟Oprah说的那句话
Sweetheart,it's like Maya Angelou keeps telling Oprah,and I keep telling you:
当你知道的越多 你做的越好
When you know better,you do better.
哇 你好知性哦
Wow,you are so wise.
要是你是直男我就跟你约会了
I wish you were straight so I could date you.
这样啊…
Well...
事实上 我还有一个迷人的 双胞胎弟弟 直男哦
as a matter of fact,I have an extremely attractive straight twin brother!
嗨
Oh,hi.
我把那张好莱坞的照片裁了
I cropped that Halloween photo.
现在只剩盐和胡椒了 看上去是不是很蠢
It's just salt and pepper,now,so it looks ridiculous.
-Ted 我想让你穿回那件团队宝宝的衣服 -什么!
- Ted,I want you back on Team Baby. - What?
我就知道你会明白的
I knew you'd come around!
伙计们 照片我没真裁
Guys! I didn't really crop the photo!
而且
Plus...
还有一个好消息
Good news.
我去报了育婴课
I signed us up for a birthing class.
这也太傻了吧
Well,that's insane.
Marshall你觉不觉得这有点太早啦
It's way too early for that,right,Marshall?
好吧 听着
Okay,listen.
我是这个孩子的爸爸 我投支持票 去上育婴课
I am the father of this child,and I vote that we go to the birthing class.
坚决不要
Absolutely not.
那这样 Lily
'Kay,Lily.
我讨厌出这张牌
I hate to play this card...
但你要是不来上这个课
but if you don't come to this class...
我就不过性生活
I'm withholding sex.
我不觉得她会来诶
I don't think she's coming.
是啊
Yeah.
当她说坐另一辆出租车的时候 我就开始怀疑了
I was a little suspicious when she had us take separate cabs.
Lily 别吃
Lily,don't do it!
一点点没关系
Just a little bit.
为我们的宝宝想想
Think about our baby!
Robin别再忽悠我了 赶紧说正紧的
You got to be kidding me,Robin. Get to the assault.
那好吧
Okay,fine.
我跟Barney一起收拾好他的公寓
So Barney and I were finishing packing his apartment...
好啦
Okay.
清单上的最后一项
One last item on the checklist.
取消冷不防电话5000
Disconnect the Cold Call 5000.
那他妈的是什么玩意?
What the hell's that?
我从一家出售身体亮粉和高端防晒霜的公司
I was able to secure the customer database from a company
搞到了绝密客户资料
that sells body glitter and high-end pasties.
那个冷不防电话5000就会给 所有22到23岁之间的女客户打电话
The Cold Call 5000 will dial every female client between the ages of 22 and 23
然后留言说
and leave the following message:
嗨 我知道这很疯狂 但我在地铁上看见你了 我知道我们就是天生一对
Hi,I know this is crazy,but I saw you on the subway,and I knew we were meant to be.
如果你相信命运的话  今晚来MacLaren酒吧找我 我是Barney Stinson
If you believe in destiny,come to MacLaren's tonight and find me,Barney Stinson.
因为我能感觉到 我应该在你身上 在你身边
Because I have this feeling that I'm supposed to be on you-- with you.
干嘛不重录一下啊?
Why not re-record it?
我录了一百来遍
I did like a hundred takes.
删不完了
It kept happening.
哎 Lily竟然不来!
I can't believe Lily's not coming!
妈的!
You know what? Screw it!
谁说俩兄弟就不能搞定个育婴课啊?
Who says that two bros can't rock a birthing class?
就是!
Rock it!
今天 我们要探讨的是 "飘飘欲仙的按摩"
Today,we'll be exploring "The Sensual Massage."
首先 让我们轻轻捧起伴侣的手
Let's start by gently cupping our partner's hands...
然后感受彼此的呼吸
and just breathe each other in.
Robin 谢谢
Thanks,Robin.
你是惟一 一个会帮我这一切的人
You're the only person I know who would help me do all that.
你真是个好哥们
You're a real bro.
不是吧?
Am I,though?
因为怎么说我也是女的
'Cause I'm really more of a woman.
敬我的女性气质
To my femininity.
不 你更像个兄弟
Nah,you're more of a bro.
你是个伙计 纯爷们!
You're a dude. You're a man.
嘿 你还可以再单身一晚
Hey,you are flying solo one more night.
我去打扮的性感热辣  你去穿件马甲把那根丑的要死的领带遮住
How about I put on a smokin' hot dress,you slap a vest over that crime scene of a tie
我们去狂欢作乐一番怎么样?
and we paint the town?
我们都多久没穿上凸现我们的性别的一身 出去狂闹烂醉了
I mean,when was the last time we got rip-roaring drunk in clothing that highlights our genders?
所以你的计划是穿的特别挑逗  去和别的女人的男人出去喝酒作乐?
So,your plan was to be out on the town,dressed provocatively,drinking with another woman's man.
Robin 这是我们第一次会诊  我知道这只是门诊建议 但...
Robin,this is our first session,and I know this is just one clinical opinion,but...
你真荡!
you a dawg!
是阿...
Yeah...
只有一个问题...
There was just one problem...
惊喜!
NORA: Surprise!
我提前回来了!
I got back early!
嘿!
Hey!
我来猜猜 你又趴在桌子底下喝多了
Let me guess,you got drunk under your desk again?
没有 哈佛先生
No,Mr. Harvard.
我这次处理的不太一样...
I handled things a little differently...
那么我想现在你要让我谈谈我当时的感受
So,I suppose now you want me to talk about how it felt
看着Barney和Nora一起离开 对不?
watching Barney and Nora walk off together,right?
我更想跳过直接谈骚扰事件
I'd rather just skip ahead to the assault.
我下一个病人觉得自己是上帝
My next patient thinks he's God.
万一他真的是对的呢 我可不想让他等太久
On the off chance that he's right,I really don't want to keep him waiting.
就在他们离开之后 发生了件疯狂的事
Well,right after they left,something crazy happened.
打扰一下 你知道Barney Stinson在哪么?
Excuse me,do you know where I can find Barney Stinson?
他在地铁上见到过我 留下消息让我来这找他
He saw me on the subway and left me a message to meet him here.
为什么不重录一下?
Why not re-record it?
我录了一百来遍
I did like a hundred takes.
删不完了
It kept happening.
嗨 我知道这很疯狂 但我在地铁上见过你...
Hi,I know this is crazy,but I saw you on the subway...
他问我是否相信命运
He asked me if I believed in destiny.
我相信
And I do.
我们天生一对
We are so meant to be.
我怎么能找到他?
Where can I find him?
我陷入了道德上的两难境地
So I was faced with a moral dilemma.
把这个傻泡推给他们 或者做个好人 帮助我朋友
Unleash this nut bag on them or be a bigger person,and help my friend.
Barney在爱之咖啡店 75街和阿姆斯特丹大街路口
Barney's at Café L'Amour,75th and Amsterdam.
太好了!
Awesome!
不 等等等!
No,wait,wait,wait!
好吧 这样不对
Okay,this isn't right.
衣扣再解开点 秀出事业线
Let's pop that top button,show off your gals.
祝你好运 去搞定他们!
Ooh! Good luck,go get 'em!
让你的爱传递到指尖
Let your love me through your fingers.
哥们 说好不哼哼 始终保持眼睛睁开
Dude,the rule is no moaning and keep your eyes open at all times.
别怪里怪气的
Stop being weird.
嘿 什么时候轮到我做女的啊?
And hey,when do I get to be the woman?
记住 怀孕期间最重要的是让妈妈淡定愉快
Now remember,the most important thing in pregnancy is to keep Mom calm and happy.
她最知道自己需要什么了
She knows best what she needs.
相信她
Trust her.
现在 爸爸们 我需要你们握住妈妈们的手
Now,Papas,I want you to take Mom's hands in yours
深深地望着她的眼睛 跟我重复
look deep into her eyes,and repeat after me.
我相信你
I believe in you.
我敬仰你身体的智慧
I honor your body's wisdom.
你的子宫是个神殿
Your womb is a temple.
- 你的子宫是 - 好了 我知道了!
- Your womb is a - Okay,I get it!
我们真不应该不听Lily的需要
I feel terrible we didn't listen to what Lily wanted!
我知道 我也是
I know,so do I.
事实是 我本以为我这会已经结婚了  和你们一起经历这些事情
The truth is,I thought I'd be married by now and going through all this stuff alongside you guys.
但就算我下一秒钟就遇到我的梦中情人 我还是要等一晚上加九个月才能有自己的家庭
But even if I meet the girl of my dreams right this second,I'm still one night and nine months away from having a family of my own.
还要假设我孩子的母亲是个荡妇的前提下
And that's assuming the mother of my children is just a huge slut.
不要放弃希望 Ted
Don't lose hope,Ted.
荡妇就在那
That slut is out there.
谢谢你兄弟
Thanks,buddy.
- 我们要向Lily道歉 - 对
- We owe Lily an apology. - Yeah.
爸爸们 现在我将要回答你们对阴道的所有问题
Dads,this is the time that I'll answer every question you've ever had about vaginas.
妈的!
Damn it!
嘿
Hey.
真对不起 Lily
I'm so sorry,Lily.
你可以就吃一点
You have just a little bit.
我意识到我的责任是 要让你在接下来的七个月保持开心
I realize now that it's my job for the next seven months to keep you happy
所以...
and that's why...
所以性生活恢复了
I'm no longer withholding sex.
我的英雄
My hero.
但我需要你不要对Sonya医生感到别扭
But I want to make sure that you feel comfortable with Dr. Sonya,too.
不会 你知道么 其实她很淡定
I do. And you know what,the fact that she's so calm
很放松 或许不是坏事
and laid back,maybe that's not a bad thing.
也许这正是生产时我们需要的
Maybe that's exactly what we're gonna want in that delivery room.
Lily 你再不用力 我就把孩子推到你嗓子眼
Lily,if you don't push,I will shove this baby up your throat
从你嘴里拽出来!
and pull it out of your mouth!
Marshall尼玛的在哪?!
Where the hell is Marshall?!
那段故事可不得了 孩子们
That's a crazy story,kids.
我以后再说
I'll get to that.
嘿 Ted在门口呢
Hey,Ted's out in the hall.
他也想道歉
He wants to apologize,too.
嘿
Hey.
你的袜子呢?
What happened to your sock?
说来话长
Long story.
说到底 我认识到有时爱意味着要让步
Bottom line,I realized that sometimes love means taking a step back.
也不尽然
Well,not always.
我是说 有时候最好干涉一下搞点蓄意破坏对吧?
I mean,sometimes it's better to interfere and sabotage stuff,right?
我觉得如果你真在乎某人 应该让他们开心
Well,I think if you care about somebody,you should want them to be happy
即使要让自己置身事外
even if you wind up being left out.
哇
Wow.
你在Lily和Marshall那边的教训还真适合我的情况
The lesson you learned with Lily and Marshall is directly applicable to my situation
因此这也正是我最终处理这件事情的关键部分
and is therefore a valid part of how I'll eventually tell this story.
真的? 真是这样的?
Really? That's how that went down?
重点是 最终都联系到一起了对吧?
Point is,it all tied together,right?
根本没有
Not really at all.
我们能不能说骚扰部分了?
Can we just get to the assault?
敬我们!
To us!
Barney 是我!
Barney,it's me!
我爱你 Barney!
I love you,Barney!
扇贝看着不错
Mmm,scallops look good.
可不是么
Oh,they are.
不过上次我点的时候卖完了 所以...
But the last time I was here they ran out,so,uh...
祝...
knock...
好...
on...
运
wood.
我想要这个紫色的蛋糕做甜点
Well,I have my eye on the red velvet cake for dessert.
不错 AA制?
Lovely. Splitsies?
不 我来买单
Nah,I want it all to myself.
真的?
Really?
掰手腕决胜负?
Arm wrestle for it?
不!
No!
好吧
All right.
我喜欢这里
I love this place.
- 谢谢你 亲爱的 - 不客气 亲爱的
- Thank you,babe. - You're welcome. Babe.
Barney对这事一点都不知道
Barney doesn't know a thing about any of this.
但这也是为什么我要接受法院强制性治疗
But that's why I got court-mandated therapy.
你肯定觉得我很傻
You must think I'm nuts.
我觉得你真是个不错的朋友
I think you're a really good friend.
- 真的? - 真的
- Really? - Really.
在我看来这起骚扰事件中没有任何犯罪倾向
As far as I'm concerned,there was no criminal inte to this assault.
谢谢 医生
Well,thanks,Doc!
看我们啊!
Well,look at us!
我们一期治疗就解决了
We got this wrapped up in one session.
干得好 对吧?
Go us,right?
现在我们谈谈你撬法官车锁的事情
Now let's discuss how you keyed the judge's car.
好吧 嗯...
Okay. Um...
事情是这样的
Here's how it happened
Marshall和Lily本来要去动物园
Marshall and Lily were supposed to go to the zoo
都会联系到一起的 我保证
okay,it all ties together,I swear.
现在...
Now...